你未来的客户会从哪儿来
Where will your next customers come from?
我给你个提示
I&#39;ll give you a hint.
他们在这个圈中
It&#39;s inside this circle.
另外  火狐浏览器的性能调整工具有了很大的变化
Plus, Firefox Performance Tools get a major overhaul.
我是Rob Doson
I&#39;m Rob Dodson.
这里是Lazy Web节目
This is Lazy Web.
新兴的市场有望增加数亿的网络新用户
Emerging markets are expected to add billions of new users
所以  我们该如何准备呢
to the web, so how do we prepare?
Opera公司的Bruce Lawson列出了全球热门的域名
Bruce Lawson of Opera highlights the top domains
这些域名表明了大家对互联网的期望是一致的
from around the world and demonstrates
that everyone wants the same internet
但并不是所有互联网事物都生来平等
but not all networks are created equal.
就像可安装的网页式程序  根据分辨率自动调整的图片
Covering topics like installable web apps, responsive images,
代理浏览器  在未来的平台中  他们会让你大开眼界
and proxy browsers, it&#39;s an eye opening look
at the future of the platform.
你可以在视频下面的说明中得到相关的链接
You can grab the link down in the Show Notes.
快捷列表参考手册
The Accessibility Cheat Sheet takes
可以帮助你解决某些在处理网站易用性中出现的麻烦
some of the pain out of making your site accessible.
基于WCAG
Based on the Web Content Accessibility Guidelines,
参考手册提供了一个清单
the cheat sheet gives checklist examples
列出了你的网站所需要支持的功能  同时提供一个
for features your site should support and also provides
可视化的示例和一些工具链接
visual examples and links to useful tools,
就像Lea Verou的对比度比例检查工具
such as Lea Verou&#39;s Contrast Ratio Checker.
数据显示85%的美国零售商的移动端流量来自于网页
Statistics show that 85% of US retailers&#39; mobile traffic
并且带来了90%的收益
is on the web and it accounts for 90% of their revenue.
Alex Komoroke 和 Elisabeth Morant
Alex Komoroke and Elisabeth Morant
在Google I/O上讲述了在网络销售的三个要点
explain the three selling points of the web platform--
实现  表现和承诺
reach, performance, and engagement--
在  讨论高级特性  环节中
in this talk from Google I/O. The talk features high level
解释了一些新的特性  像安装标语
explanations of new features, like install banners
和通知  同样还展示了数据的大小
and notifications, as well as data
在网络金融的冲击
demonstrating the size and financial impact of the web.
看一看火狐开发版中最新的开发工具包
Take a look at the latest DevTools in Firefox Developer Edition.
瀑布流效果  强调了可调整帧率
Waterfall View highlights frame rate changes
和相应的时间线事件
and corresponding events on the timeline,
等大量的JavaScript内容
such as heavy JavaScript work.
调用关系树  的功能耗光了
The Call Tree summarizes which functions eat up
你应用程序中的大部分资源
the most time in your application,
火焰图  能帮你发现
and the Flame Chart helps you decide
是否有应用程序运行了太长时间
if a function took a very long time to run
或者被调用太多次
or may have just been called too many times.
这个视频同时还强调了如何使用  网页工作者  来加快
This video also highlights using Web Workers to speed up
你的应用程序
your application.
你可以在下面的说明中找到相应的链接
You can check out the link down in the description.
使用下一代HTTP协议可以减少网络中的一些潜在问题  会使整个网络更快
Decreasing network latency with HTTP2 will make the entire web faster.
今年的Velocity Con上Ilya Grigorik的PPT
Ilya Grigorik&#39;s slides from this year&#39;s Velocity Con
看到了下一代HTTP协议将会从根本上
look at the ways that HTTP2 will radically
改变我们如何去创建高性能应用程序
change how we build performant applications.
不再直接连接你的资源
Stop concatenating your resources
并集中于优化缓存  删除域名碎片
and focus on better caching, remove domain sharding,
并且让服务器推送和取代你现有的  inlining strategies  组件
and let server push replace your current inlining strategies.
你可以在视频下面的说明中找到所有的幻灯片
You can see the full slide deck down in the Show Notes.
大伙们  以上就是本周要说的
That&#39;s it for this week, folks.
你将会在视频下面的说明中找到所有相关的链接
Links to everything are down in the Show Notes.
请点击下面的订阅小按钮
Click that little Subscribe button.
献给Lazy Web的爱好者，谢谢观看
And to you Lazy Webers out there, thanks for watching.
[播放音乐]
[MUSIC PLAYING]